Searching for the Wendigo is a documentary film directed by Larry Fessenden.
Documentary short for Larry Fessenden’s 2001 feature film, WENDIGO.
Self, played by Larry Fessenden.
Self, played by Jake Weber.
Self, played by Patricia Clarkson.
Self, played by Erik Per Sullivan.
Laurence T.
Fessenden (born March 23, 1963) is an American actor and filmmaker.
He is the founder of the New York based independent
production outfit Glass Eye Pix.
His writer/director credits include No Telling (written with Beck Underwood, 1991), Habit (1997), Wendigo (2001), and The Last
Winter (written with Robert Leaver, 2006), which is in the permanent collection of the Museum of Modern Art.
He has also directed the television feature Beneath (2013), an episode of the NBC TV series Fear Itself (2008)
entitled "Skin and Bones", and a segment of the anthology horror-comedy film The ABCs of Death 2 (2014).
He is the writer, with Graham Reznick, of the BAFTA
Award-winning Sony PlayStation video game Until Dawn.
Films he has acted in include Bringing Out the Dead (1999), Broken Flowers (2005), I Sell the Dead (2009), Jug Face (2012), We Are Still Here (2015), In
a Valley of Violence (2016), Like Me (2017), and The Dead Don't Die (2019), Brooklyn 45 (2023), and Killers of the Flower Moon (2023).